Woman's Club of Albany; Records mss139
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Financials, 1910-2019; 2; 6.2 cubic ft.
  - Civic Section, Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1927; 1934; Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Business Meetings and Club Day Expenses and Various Receipts, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Conservation Department Expenses, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Public Education Department Expenses, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - House Committee Expenses, 1930-1931; 1936-1937; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bank Statements, 1930-1932; 1934 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1930-1939 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Hospitality Committee Expenses, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Language Department Expenses, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Business Meetings and Club Day Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Conservation Department Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Dramatic Department and Music Department Expenses, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Social Committee Expenses, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Art Department Expenses, 1932-1934; 1940; Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Social Committee Expenses and Receipts, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Conservation Department Expenses, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Dramatic Department Expenses, 1933-1934; 1936; 1939 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Music Department Expenses, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Expenses, 1933-1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Hospitality Committee Expenses, 1933-1934; 1937 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bank Statements, 1935-1939 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Ledger, 1936-1943 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Altruistic Committee Ledger, 1936-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cash Book, 1938-1947 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - American Home Department Expenses, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Garden Department Expenses, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Language and Literature Department Expenses, 1939-1940; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Social Committee Expenses for Business Meetings, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bank Statements, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments (1 of 2), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments (2 of 2), 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ledger, 1943-1950 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cash Book, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sales Accounts, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bank Statements, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rentals, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Day Book/Cash Book, 1947-1960 (Box 2)
  - Completed Forms on Behalf of Employees, 1948; 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Rentals, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ledger, 1950-1957 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bank Statements, 1950; 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Youth Co-Operation Department Card Party Expenses, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1951-1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bazaar Card Party Expenses, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Garden Department Flower Show Expenses, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Report on Safety Deposit Box, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Ledger, 1956-1960 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Messenger Expenses, 1959; 1964; 1972-1973; Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Ledger, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Cash Book, 1961-1975 (Box 2)
  - Federal Tax Returns and IRS Correspondence, 1961-1966; 1972-1973; 1994-2009 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Membership Dues Ledger, 1962-1998 (Box 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Rentals, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYS Women's Legislative Form Dues, 1964-1971; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Tax Exemption Forms (1 of 2), 1964-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tax Exemption Forms (2 of 2), 1964-2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1965-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1966-1976; 1996; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Lease on the Woman's Club Property, 1970-1971; 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bank Statements, 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Financial Ledger, 1973-1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bank Statements, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Church Receipts, 1975-1978; Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Account Book, 1976-1982 (Box 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Resolution by Board for Bank and Banking Responsibilities, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Bank Statements, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Completed Grant Applications, 1980-1981; 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1980-1994 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1981 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1982 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1983 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements, 1983-1989 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1984 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1985 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1986 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1987 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1988 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1989 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1990 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Bank Statements, 1990-1995 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Cash Book, 1990-1996 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1991 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1992 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1993 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1994 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Legal Advice, 1994-1996 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1995 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Insurance Policies and Payments, 1995-2005 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1996 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - Bank Statements, 1996-1999 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - Cash Book, 1996-2000 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - Card Party Expenses, 1997 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1997 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1998 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Bank Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 1999 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2000 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - Bank Statements, 2000-2005 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2001 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2004 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, 2005 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - Payment Documents, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - Financial Support, 2005; 2016; Undated (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Grants, 2005-2006; 2008-2010 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 37)
  - Budget and Financial Documents, 2005-2009 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Treasury, 2006-2007 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 39)
  - Financial Statements, 2007 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 40)
  - Funds and Grants, 2007 (Box 6 (2-Financials), Folder 41)
  - Donations, 2008-2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Donations and Planning, 2008-2010; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - Financials, 2010; 2016 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Finances and Contributions, 2014; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Gifts, 2015 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - Yearly Budget, 2015 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - Donation Proposals, 2015; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Fundraising, 2016 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - Funding, 2017; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Donations and Funding, 2018; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - Financial, 2019 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - Forms, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - General Receipts and Expenses, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Member Expenses Book, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - Music Section Expenses, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - Sales Book, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - Social Committee Expenses, Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
- Departments and Committees, 1911-2017; 3; 1.2 cubic ft.
  This series contains the annual reports of different departments and committees. The reports give news about each department or committee from the year, and their respective future plans. Most reports are typed, but some of the original handwritten reports sent to the Board secretary are included as well. In addition, there are meeting minutes from select committees.
  - Dramatic Department, 1911-1915; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Parliamentary Law Department Minutes, 1912-1918 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - Municipal Welfare Department Book, 1913-1918 (Box 7 (2-Financials))
  - Meeting Minutes, 1919 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Department and Committees Directory, Lists of Duties and Committee Rules, 1919-1946; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1920-1921 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1921-1922 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1922-1923 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Travelers' Aid Committee, 1922-1924; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - Original Annual Committee Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Typewritten Annual Committee Reports, 1923-1924 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 10)
  - A Program of Community Study, Possibly Used by Municipal Welfare Department, 1924 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (1 of 2), 1924-1925 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (2 of 2), 1924-1925 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (1 of 2), 1925-1928 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments (2 of 2), 1925-1928 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 15)
  - Garden Section Yearbook, 1927-1928 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 16)
  - Annual Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1928-1934 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 17)
  - Annual Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1928-1934 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 18)
  - Secretary Report and Garden Section Reports, 1931-1942 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 19)
  - Annual Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1934-1938 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 20)
  - Annual Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1934-1938 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 21)
  - Committee Directories, 1935-1941 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 22)
  - Altruistic Committee, 1937-1941 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 23)
  - Annual Committee Reports (1 of 2), 1938-1943 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 24)
  - Annual Committee Reports (2 of 2), 1938-1943 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 25)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1944-1951 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 26)
  - Garden Department, 1950-1951; 1957; 1962 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 27)
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1952 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 28)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1956-1957 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1957-1958 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 30)
  - Annual Department Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 31)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1958-1959 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 32)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1959-1960 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 33)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1960-1961 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 34)
  - Annual Reports of the Departments, 1961-1962 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 35)
  - Annual Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 36)
  - Annual Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 37)
  - Annual Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 38)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 39)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 40)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 41)
  - Garden Department, 1970-1973 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 42)
  - Department Reports, 1971 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 43)
  - Committee Lists, 2006 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 44)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 2006 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 45)
  - Building Committee Report, 2006; 2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 46)
  - Committee Lists, 2006; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 47)
  - Garden Committee, 2007; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 48)
  - Committee Reports, 2007; 2009-2010; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 49)
  - Finance Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 50)
  - Garden Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 51)
  - Governance Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 52)
  - Committee Information, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 53)
  - Fundraising Committee, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 54)
  - Membership Committee, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 1)
  - Rental Committee, 2008-2009; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 3)
  - Building Committee Meeting Agenda, 2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 4)
  - Building Committee Report, 2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 5)
  - Centennial Committee, 2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 6)
  - Communications Committee Report, 2009 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 7)
  - Committee Organizations, 2010-2012; Undated (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 8)
  - Committee Reports, 2015 (Box 7 (2-Financials), Folder 9)
  - Committee Reports, 2016 (Box 2 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 10)
  - Committee Activity, 2017 (Box 2 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 11)
  - Annual Department Reports, Undated (Box 2 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 12)
  - Garden Section Annual Report and Member List, Undated (Box 2 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 13)
  - Housing Committee Rules, Undated (Box 2 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 14)
  - International Affairs Annual Report, Undated (Box 2 (3-Departments and Committees), Folder 15)
- Membership, 1910-2015; 4; 3.2 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically within subseries 1, 2, 4 and 5.
  Arranged chronologically within subseries 3.
  This series is comprised of five subseries and documents various aspects of Womans Club of Albany membership. There are applications for new members which range from 1938-2004. At first the applications were kept by themselves in stacks by year. Then, starting in 1968, the WCA began attaching a copy the Clubs acceptance letter to the new member application. The last few sets of dates (1994, 1996, 2001, and 2004) revert back to the original filing format; without an acceptance letter attached. These membership applications and acceptance letters are filed chronologically.
  The WCA also kept resignation records. It did this in various ways, including index cards and resignation letters. The index cards begin as handwritten cards and transition to typed cards. Amongst the resignations are index cards of members dropped because of unpaid dues. These index cards are grouped into three different categories to maintain original order. Beginning in the 1960s, the WCA started keeping track of resignation letters and letters from the WCA acknowledging the member's resignation. The WCA also kept records of member deaths.
  As with Series 7, Publications, the Womans Club of Albany often changed the layout of the information it published. Every year, the Club produced a new membership list. From 1917-1929, the WCA published membership lists as booklets. In 1933 the WCA switched and began publishing membership lists as pamphlets. As the WCA also switched to monthly news pamphlets around this time, it suggests the WCA mailed out a new membership list, with the monthly news, and the Officers, Departments, and Committees Directory pamphlet once every year. From 1968-1971 the Club published a combination of the Officers Directory and membership in a small booklet.
  Please note that from 1911-1942 the Womans Club of Albany would typically make the Governor of New Yorks wife an honorary member. This included Eleanor Roosevelt during Franklin Delano Roosevelt's tenure as governor. It is unknown when and why this tradition stopped.
  - Early Member Index Cards, 1910-1931; 4.1
    - Index cards, A-Y, 1910-1931, Undated (Box 3)
  - Early Membership Applications and Resignations, 1917-1927; 4.2
    - Early Membership Applications A, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Early Membership Applications B, 1917-1924 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Early Membership Applications C, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Early Membership Applications D, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Early Membership Applications E, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Early Membership Applications F, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Early Membership Applications G, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Early Membership Applications H, I, &J, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Early Membership Applications K &L, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Early Membership Applications M, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Early Membership Applications N &O, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Early Membership Applications P &Q, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Early Membership Applications R, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Early Membership Applications S, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Early Membership Applications T, U, &V, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Early Membership Applications W, 1917-1925 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Early Membership Applications Z, 1917-1923 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Early Resignations, A, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Early Resignations, B, 1915-1923; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Early Resignations, C, 1915-1923; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Early Resignations, D, 1912-1921; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Early Resignations, E &F, 1911-1924; Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Early Resignations, G, 1912-1922; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Early Resignations, H, I, &J, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Early Resignations, K &L, 1912-1924; Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Early Resignations, M, 1911-1924; Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Early Resignations, N &O, 1916-1922; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Early Resignations, P, 1915-1922; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Early Resignations, R, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Early Resignations, S, 1911-1920; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Early Resignations, T, U, &V, 1915-1922; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Early Resignations, W &Y, 1911-1923; Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Early Resignations, A, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Early Resignations, B, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Early Resignations, C, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Early Resignations, D, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Early Resignations, E &F, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Early Resignations, G, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Early Resignations, H, I, &J, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Early Resignations, K &L, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Early Resignations, M, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Early Resignations, P &Q, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Early Resignations, R, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Early Resignations, S, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Early Resignations, T, U, &V, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Early Resignations, W, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Membership Files, 1910-2015; 4.3
    - New Membership Nominations, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Membership List Book, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Membership List Book (1 of 2), 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Membership List Book (2 of 2), 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Resignations, ca.1920s (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Membership List Book ( 1 of 2), 1922 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Membership List Book ( 2 of 2), 1922 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Registration Cards, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - List of Applications and Resignation, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - List of Resignations, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - New Member Lists, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Invitation to Vote and Election Ballot, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - New Members, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Membership List Book (1 of 2), 1924 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Membership List Book (2 of 2), 1924 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Paid Membership List, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Typewritten Membership List, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Membership List Book (1 of 2), 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Membership List Book (2 of 2), 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Membership List Book (1 of 3), 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Membership List Book (2 of 3), 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Membership List Book (3 of 3), 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Membership List Book, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Membership List Book, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Membership List Pamphlet, 1933; 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Blank Election Ballots, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Membership Applications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Membership Applications, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 28)